well one thing I've learned over the
years is that you can't be afraid of
failing in fact on my show when I help
businesses I fail all the time I'm
normally shy to show those moments but
tonight I'm going to make an exception
so let's take a look now at some of my
greatest
failures one of my least popular ideas
was for a completely germfree hot dog
stand at outdoor food carts it's easy
for germs to transfer from money to your
food so to completely eliminate this I
designed a handsfree method to apply
condiments to the wiener also there
would be a second employee whose only
job is to handle the money what you do
with the w we're doing a germ free
experience so you don't handle your own
money oh really but people were a bit
annoyed with the money handling part can
have my wall back and the handsfree
onion dispenser proved to be problematic
as well so you have to up one up one
down when it hits the table the onions
will fall and drop it keep dropping it
up and down drop it
fast oh this is not going to work it's
not nothing to do with the contraption
if you drop a hot dog you drop a hot dog
the public just wasn't ready for the
germ-free hot dog experience so I laid
the concept to rest next I had an idea
for a tearless way to tell a child that
their pet has died to be an upsell
service for an animal hospital the
concept was to make a video of the pet
while it's still alive telling the child
it's in animal heaven now I hired The
only voice actor that responded to my
Craigslist ad to be the dog but when we
showed it to the owner's child
oh it's me Maddie I'm in heaven now so
sorry I died I miss you so much I'm
happy here so I'm not coming home I miss
doesn't talk like that however
she it's okay he hated his dog's voice
another flubbed idea and lastly my
favorite ideas don't just help with
business they're good for the community
as well so I approached a bar with an
Innovative way to stop drunks from
getting behind the wheel the concept was
to have a street magician stationed
outside the bar performing a magic trick
that allows him to secretly test the
blood alcohol levels of patrons as they
leave and with my backgrounded magic I
offered to test it out for my final
trick I'm going to need your keys my
keys
yes great give the wand to
blow okay a little bit harder right into
the
top
okay and you over the legal limit blood
alcohol so your keys are gone and I
cannot give them back to you okay sorry
but that's when I realized the flaw in
my idea if I held on to his keys and he
took a cab the guy couldn't get into his
apartment could I get my keys please I
can't because you're drunk please give
me my keys and the only solution at that
point was to drive him home you live far
I know I do also once I got him home I
realized I couldn't just give him his
keys until he was asleep or else he
might go out and drive again you need to
see me sleeping I need to see you fall
asleep before I leave your keys or else
you might take them and go out
again you don't brush your teeth before
bed and usually not I usually brush my
teeth in the morning really yep I know
it's kind of gross but nobody else is
really paying attention to the way my
breath smells so I had to put him to bed
and make sure he went to sleep and if
that looking glass gets broke mama's
going to get you a billy goat before I
left his
keys so as you can see even the greatest
Minds fail
sometimes